Nguyen Minh Huy

Front-End Developer · Fresher

O Dist. 12 gmail@huy.dev







Summary

A **dedicated** and **hardworking** individual seeking a challenging role as a Frontend Developer at a progressive organization that provides tremendous growth opportunities and allows me to apply my knowledge and skills to help the organization succeed. In the first 2 years, I want to become a Fullstack Developer (Back-End, Front-End, Devops,...). After 5 years, I will become a **Team leader**.

Education

Ho Chi Minh City University of Education

i Oct 2020 - Oct 2024

Software Technology - GPA: 3.5 / 4

Work Experience

WALA ICT VIET NAM — Front-End Developer

🗐 Jan 2024 - May 2024

Project APFRAS (12/03/2024 - 30/04/2024)

Description: Web project promoting collaboration among 9 member countries. APFRAS,

based in Korea, serves as a forum for events, news, and updates. Members can create admin accounts for specific information access, similar to an

 $association\,website\,for\,food\,safety\,initiatives.$

Role: Front-End Developer

■ **Tech Stack:** Front-End User: NextJS + Typescript + TailwindCSS

Front-End Admin: ReactTS + TailwindCSS

Back-End: Java Spring Boot Database: PostgreSQL

Website: https://apfrasofficial.org/

Project PUDDING-PAY (19/10/2023 - 19/04/2024)

Description:
A website that provides information for individuals interested in establishing

franchise businesses.

Role: Front-End Developer

■ **Tech Stack:** Front-End User: NextJS + Typescript + TailwindCSS

 $Front-End\,Admin:\,ReactTS+TailwindCSS$

Back-End: NestJS Database: PostgreSQL

Website: https://pudding-pay.com/

Project LGSI (07/122023 - 05/04/2024)

Description: Create landing pages for the LG&SI services.

Role: Front-End Developer

■ **Tech Stack:** Front-End User: NextTS + TailwindCSS

Front-End Admin: ReactTS + TailwindCSS

Back-End: Java Spring Boot Database: PostgreSQL

Website: https://sni.co.kr/

Project HANWHA-LIFE (06/12/2023-24/04/2024)

Description:
This project involves developing a user interface focused on managing

devices.

Role: Front-End Developer

■ **Tech Stack:** Front-End: ReactJS + Typescript + Tailwindcss + ThreeJS

Project DANGPRO (05/03/2024 - 15/06/2024)

Description: A website that provides information for individuals interested in establishing

franchise businesses.

Role: Front-End Developer

■ **Tech Stack:** Admin: ReactJS + Typescript + Tailwind

Mobile: React-native

Project EDUIN (15/03/2024 - 15/06/2024)

Description: The goal of this project is to create a user interface for obtaining

certifications.

Role: Front-End Developer

■ **Tech Stack**: Front-End: ReactJS + Typescript + Tailwindcss

FREELANCER — Front-End Developer

iii May 2024 - Now

Project Job Network (01/05/2024 - 31/05/2024)

Description:
A job site in Vietnam, Focus on IT work, and create websites tailored to the

needs and preferences of IT candidates.

Role: Front-End Developer

■ **Tech Stack**: Front-End User: NextJS + Typescript + TailwindCSS

Front-End Admin: ReactTS + TailwindCSS

Back-End: Java Spring Boot

Website: https://heydevs-fe-admin.vercel.app/

Personal Projects

Mooment Store - Mechanical keyboard store

Description: Mooment is an online store that sells mechanical keyboards. Customers have

a new experience thanks to the user-friendly interface and numerous outstanding features. The website has many basic and new features, such as a voucher list, online payment via PayPal, emailing invoices to customers, and so on. The website is SEO-optimized for sharing across multiple platforms,

 $including \ Facebook, Google, Twitter, and others.\\$

Role: Fullstack Developer

Website:

■ **Tech Stack:** Front-End User: NextTS + TailwindCSS

Back-End: ExpressJS + NodeJS

Database: MongoDB https://mooment.vercel.app/

Kruskal and Floyd - Visualization algorithm application

Description: Begin your visual exploration of graph algorithms by thoroughly examining the

Kruskal and Floyd algorithms. Discover how Kruskal's method meticulously uncovers the Minimum Spanning Tree in weighted graphs, whereas the dynamic Floyd algorithm expertly navigates directed weighted graphs, illuminating optimal paths even with a wide range of edge weights, both

positive and negative.

Role: Fullstack Developer

Tech Stack: HTML5, CS3, Javascript, CanvasWebsite: https://mykruskalandfloyd.app

Skills & Tools

Languages

FE related HTML CSS/SCSS TypeScript JavaScript

BErelated Javascript SQL NoSQL

Technologies

Ul related Tailwind CSS Material Ul Ant Design

FE related React Next.js GSAP Redux React-hook-form

BE related Express MongoDB

Tools & Softwares

Coder related VS Code Node.js Git Github Desktop

Designer related Figma